Hello Bhai Memon, in today's video we are going to
talk in detail about the
most value for money variant of Maruti Suzuki Atiga
which comes in the name of VXI CNG.
If you also plan for Atiga then
you get two variants in VXI variant.  First of all is
VXI and second is VXI
Plus CNG.  So what the CNG variant has is
that you get the option of CNG.
Besides this, you will also
get very good mileage with CNG.  If you are
planning to buy a car for personal use or
commercial use, where you
get good mileage and all the
necessary features, then you
must check out this car which
comes in the name of VXI CNG.  What features are you
getting, what price are you going to get,
how much are you getting on offer, we will
talk about everything in this video.  What mileage are you going to get
?  How many engine options are available?  Let's
clear everything in this video.  First of all, if we
talk about the price, then the
showroom price of this particular variant is approximately Rs
10,76,300.
Rest now I am Hindustan
Auto Edge NC which is available in Hazaribagh Jharkhand.
Here it is doing on road cost
approx ₹1,45,000 and this
price is the latest price.  If we
talk about offers etc., then
you will not find any offer on this car right now.  You
can see from the front that it
looks something which looks very nice.
You are going to get a ground clash of 185 mm here.
You will get headlights in two shapes here.  Meaning it will be
available in dual shape.  One projector, one
reflector.  Here in the projector you are getting
low beam, in the reflector you are getting high beam.
Here you will get parking, here
you will get side indicator light.
Fog lights are not available in this variant.
You can get it installed as an accessory.
You are getting this type of grill
which is with chrome.  Here you will
find the Suzuki logo.
You all can put number plates here.  Rest below
you are going to get ready water grill also.
You get something like this in the bonnet.
Two wipers and two washers are available.  The
windshield is also going to be quite large.  And
in the front windshield you get a CNG
sticker here and here you can
see a regular antenna in front.
Now if we talk about the side profile, you
all can see that it looks like this from the side
which looks quite good.
In this variant, you are
getting tyres with black steel rims which are from
Bridge Stone Company.  If we
talk about the rest of the profile etc., then the profile
you are getting is 18565 R 15 inches.
You are getting 15 inch tables tyre here.
You get disc brakes in the front tyre and drum brakes in the rear tyre.  On the side,
you will get it in body color with
LED side turn indicators and B pillar is in
matte black and C pillar is
in matte black here.
You can fill the rest of the fuel from the left side which
comes with 45 litre petrol capacity
in which you will get the support of 82 litres of petrol
and you can also fill CNG from here
which will fill 8 to 9 kg easily.
Rest you are getting the security button here.
If this knob remains open
then the car will not start.  You will have to
close it properly.  Only then will the
car start.  And
from the back it looks something which
looks quite nice.  Here you will
see a spoiler in which you will
get a high speed stop lap.
You can get the CNG sticker here.
And you will get tail light something like this.
Here you will get both main brake and parking
lights.  You can get side indicator
reverse light here.   The
rest is the Suzuki logo, Attiga branding
and in this variant you only
get four parking sensors in the reverse.  I ca
n't find the camera etc.  You
can install it as an accessory because inside you will
get Tudon's music system.
Now let's open its boot.  To open the boot,
you get a lever here
through which you can open the boot.
And here you will
get the same amount of boot space.  Otherwise, if you want to
increase the boot space, you will have to fold both the seats of the third row.
So
you are going to get a huge boot space here and
you are going to get a CNG tank here
which you can all see completely, it is
available here with protection.  So
I have clarified everything about the exterior of this car, the difference in new price and whatever features you were getting.  Now let's move
towards the interior of this car and see
what premium features are available in the interior.  So
now let's start with the interior.
First, from the passenger side door
handle.  You can see that in this variant
you are going to get door handles in body color.  The
rest of the interior trim is something
that
looks quite good.  You are going to get the best type of
color here.  The good
thing is that in this variant you
get power window controls at the rear.
Along with the rest of the chrome, the door has its own lock
button, speaker, both magnifying glass
and a little space is also available here.
In this variant, you get a four-speaker
setup in all four doors and you
can see the seat colour and the interior colour will be something like this.   First of all,
start from the third row.
To access the third row,
you get this lever behind both the seats here and here,
through which this seat folds.
And you will have to push like this with your hand.
So it will go this far and
you will get this much area inside to access.
First of all, you
can see here that in this variant you are
getting 50 and 50 split seats.  Apart from this,
you are getting two adjustable head rests here.
You are also getting seat belt here.
And you will
also be able to recline both these seats backwards.  You can see something,
you get so many angles here.   To
recline backwards, if you are facing
any back problem then
after reclining backwards you will get very good support in your back.
You will get fabric seats everywhere here.   You
can see the texture of the seat.  So quite
premium you are going to get the seat attacher.  If we
talk about length, then a good seat
length is available.  There is no hard seat.
You are getting a soft seat.  Talking about the rest,
in the third row you will get two AC vents
which you will be able to control from here.
Here you are getting one bottle holder and another
bottle holder.   The
glass area is also going to be quite large.   If you are
sitting in the third row then you will
not feel any suffocation.  You can find one Gab
handle here and the other Gab handle
here.  Rest here
you are getting light with regular bulb.
And if we talk about legroom etc., then
you are going to get very good space in the legroom.
You all can see the space in the second row and third row.
Something like this is going to be found.
So, I have cleared all the features that you will get in the third row of this car.
Now let's move
towards the second and first rows of this car and see
what premium features you are going to get there.
Rest start from Second Road now.
So what you have to say here is that you will
not get a 50-50 speed sheet.  Here you will get 40 and 60
speedsheets.  The remaining three you are
getting adjustable head rest.
You are getting the schedule for middle passers.  And you
can see the color of the seat.  Pretty cool you're going to
get the seat color.  If we talk about length, then a
good seat length is available.  There
is no hard seat.  Soft seat is available which is covered
with fabric.  Rest you can recline both this and this
seat backwards.
You find a lever here.
Through which, if you sit on this seat and are facing
any problem in your back, then
after reclining the back, you will
get very good support in your back.  Rest of the things,
after sitting inside, you will
get a lot of space in thigh support and leg room.
You don't find any pockets behind the driver's seat.
You get a pocket behind the driver's seat
and in the center you
get two AC vents and below
you have a Type C charger.  Rest
you will get some light space here and
you will get some hump here.
Even after being humped, three people can sit here
because you can see the length of the seat is quite
long.  Here you
also get side air bags and high adjustable seat belts.  Keeping in
mind the safety of the Tiga, you will get six air
bags along with ABSVD traction
control etc. in all the variants.
Considering safety.  From the rear, you
see a dashboard that
looks quite good.  So
I cleared all the features that were available in the second row, third row and exterior of this car.  Now let's move to the
front row of this car and see
what premiums are there in the front row.  So let's
start with the front row, first of all with the
driver's side door handle.  You can see that
in this variant you will get door handles in body color.  You will be
able to lock and unlock the car even by using the remaining key.  You all will be able to
lock and unlock the vehicle through remote side locking.
And if I show you the key, you
can see that you
get a key like this in this variant.  Two button lock unlock
with center locking.  You will
find the Suzuki logo at the back.  As for the rest, the interior
trim is something
that looks quite good.
Here you will get dual tone texture.
Door lock unlock button with chrome.
Again, you get a little
space here and control of all four power windows here.
One touch down up
you are getting a mirror.  The Marshall Lock Unlock
button is available here.  You can find the mirror lock
unlock button here.  And
side and electrically adjust and fold
buttons are also available.  Rest of the speakers, both
holders, magazine are also available.  You
can see the dashboard.  You are going to get a very premium dashboard here.
In this variant, you will
get the driver side seat only with back action.  The good thing is that
you will get air bags in both the seats.
Driver side second to driver side.
You get two adjustable headrests in the front.
Shoulder support is also going to be very good.
And if we talk about the seat length, then a
good seat length is available.  There
is no hard seat.  You are getting a soft seat.
You get the option to insert the key
here.  Here you get the
button to turn on and off the rear AC vent.  Above
you find the button to turn on traction control.
Below you can find the
button to switch between CNG and petrol.  You
all will be able to level the headlight from here.  You can find the fuel opener
here.  You can get the front bonnet opener
here.  And the company has
also provided you with all three dead pedals here.
And after sitting inside, you
see a dashboard which
looks quite premium.
Starting with the steering,
you get a flat-bottom steering in this variant.
In the middle you get the Suzuki logo and
an air bag here.   On the
left side, you get multimedia
control and telephony
control.  You will also get call receive, call cut and
Bluetooth verse cond here.
You will
not get any cruise control in this variant.  Rest on the
right side of the steering you get the control of headlight, on
the left side you get the control of wiper.  If the
steering adjustment is checked,
you will be able to adjust it only up and down and not up and down, forward and backward.
And this is its semi digital meter console which
looks very good.
Tacho meter on the left side, here you will get CNG
meter and on the right side you will get kilometer.
You can get petrol meter here.  You get the display in the middle.
People will be able to see your driving time etc. here.  The vehicle is
running on CNG or petrol.  You can
see it here.  You will get time here.
Here you will get rear seat vendor and trip
to trip also autometer everything.
With the button on the right side, you will be able to see first of all the
power, torque etc. of this vehicle, along with this you will be
able to see whether this vehicle has run more on CNG or petrol and how much fuel is there in the CNG tank,
you will be able to see all of that here and
as you open the door, which door is open,
you will get all the opening warning lights here, with the
button on the left side, you will be able to see below,
trip by trip, odometer etc.
everything else here you are going to get in this variant, a
Toot music system which is a
four speaker setup, the
company has given you inbuilt, Bluetooth
FM is ready, USB AUX etc. everything is quite
good, you are going to get a music system.
Here you will get four AC vents in the front.
In the rest of the centre, you
get the hazard switch and engine immobilizer light here.
You get manual climate control here.  Below
you will find a 12W charging socket and AUX
and USB sockets.  There is a little space
available here.  You will get the folder of two
here.  And this is its gear
of first speed gian no and one reverse.
Quite a premium you are getting gear off of.
You will find the hand brake here.  Here
you get arm rest which is slideable.
You are going to get a lot of space inside.
Talking about glove box space,
you will get decent space in the glove box also.
You will also get an air bag here.
Day and night manual IIT is available in the centre.
Here you are getting light
which is with regular bulb.  Rest of the
things, in the driver side sunset, you will get
only the ticket toller on the driver side of the mirror.
So this was the most value for money variant of Tiga.
Exterior and interior features of VXI CNG variant etc.
How did you like all these features?  All of you please comment below.
Now let's talk about the engine section of this car.
So after being front borne,
you are going to get this type of look
in this car.  Here you are getting engine insulation.
You are not provided with any engine guard below.  The
bat you are getting here will be
made of one side.  Now
talking about the engine, here you will
get two engine options in this variant.
First of all, petrol, second petrol plus
CNG and if we talk about engine specification, then
here you are going to get 1.5 L
naturally aspirated DSC CNG
petrol engine.  In terms of power and torque,
this engine generates 87 bhp of power along with
121.5 Nm of torque.  You are going to
get a lot of power and torque with this engine.  In terms
of mileage, this
engine will give you a
mileage of between 25 and 30 kmph with CNG, both in city and highway.
That too with CNG.
How did you like the rest of this car?  All of you please
comment below on this video.  If you are also
planning to buy an RT and your budget is
around Rs 12.5 lakh, then
definitely check out this VXI CNG variant.  If you are
visiting the channel for the first time then do subscribe.
See you in the next video.  Till then keep
watching, keep safe.